jysk.ca 2009-04-17

# JYSK.ca - BED BATH AND HOME - Legal Information

|  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|  |  |  |   
---|---|---|---|---  
|    

|  |    
| | Commitment to Privacy  
---|---  
 | 

At JYSK Linen’n Furniture Ltd. (“ **JYSK** ”) we know how important it is to protect your personal information and are aware of, and sensitive to, the privacy concerns of our customers and other visitors to our website. This online privacy policy describes our current information management practices and confirms out commitment to comply with the _Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act._ To increase the security of personal information being transmitted over the internet we use SSL Layer Protocol to transmit all of the information collected. Additionally, we are a registered merchant with Verisign Inc. (http://www.verisign.com), the most recognized name in the digital integration industry.

Please take the time if you have not already done so to familiarize yourself with these provisions. Please note that we may occasionally update our online privacy policy and it is your responsibility to check for such updates. Any updates to the online privacy policy will be effective the date they are posted on our website. We will change the date on our online privacy policy to indicate when any changes are made.  
  
| What Information is Collected and How is it Used?  
 | 

JYSK collects two types of information: personal information and non-personal information.

With your consent, we may use your personal information for many different purposes, for example:

  * Fulfill requests for products, services or information;
  * Provide customer service;
  * Offer new products and services; and
  * Tailor our online or retail store offerings to your preferences.

We only collect personal information from you when you voluntarily offer the information, such as when signing up for online newsletters or when you set up an account with us.

Personal information provided when you subscribe to the JYSK Mail newsletter is only used to deliver the JYSK Mail newsletter to your e-mail account and maintain the accuracy of your information. If you wish to unsubscribe, please click the unsubscribe option that appears at the bottom of every JYSK Mail.

When placing an order with us, your credit card information is encrypted using SSL protocol and sent directly to our credit card processing company, Eigen Development Ltd., where it is only stored until the completion of your transaction. You are able to modify all personal information that is stored after the completion of an online transaction by logging into your account [hyperlink to MyLogin page].

Non-personal information does not identify you as an individual. Like many other web sites, we automatically collect some non-personal information such as the website pages visited, the images that are viewed, the content that you download from the website, which website you used to connected to our website and the date and time you access the website. We use this information to track website traffic patterns which enables us to know what type of information is most useful to you so that we can improve our website and make it easier for you to access information.  
  
| Safeguarding Information  
 | 

All personal information is stored on internal network servers which are protected by firewalls from network intrusions and in a secure, alarmed data centre to protect from physical theft. Additionally, you can request to have all your personal information removed from our servers by sending an email to onlinehelpdesk@jysk.ca  
  
| Discloser of Information to Third Parties  
 | 

JYSK collects information solely for internal use and will not disclose any personal information collected to a third party unless required by law or to co-operate with local, provincial, national and international authorities in investigations of improper or unlawful activities.  
  
| Your Consent to this Agreement  
 | 

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of information by JYSK as described in this online privacy policy.

Please send any questions you have regarding our online privacy policy to onlinehelpdesk@jysk.ca
